Guide to the Erroll Garner Archive, 1942-2010 AIS.2015.09 AIS.2015.09
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Legal Documentation, IV.
  - Non-Visual Licenses, 1947-2000; 1.
    - Belltone Music Publishers- Songwriters Contracts (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Publishing Agreements, 1954-2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Publishing (Box 24, Folder 3-9)
    - Sheet Music Agreements (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Erroll Garner Miscellaneous Audio/Print Licenses (Box 24, Folder 11-26)
    - List of record label licenses issued (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Foreign Business, 1955-1967; 2.
    This subseries contains 600 foreign business correspondence and business records.
    - Correspondence, Re: Agreement between London Records and Octave, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Publishing Correspondence and Agreements (Box 25, Folder 2-16)
    - BBC (Box 26, Folder 1-13)
    - Martha Glaser correspondence with BBC TV Center (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - American Federation of Music (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Concert Contracts, 1957-1975; 3.
    - Foreign Performance Agreements, 1962-1966 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Foreign Concert Contracts, 1964-1973 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Foreign Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 18-22)
    - Editions Musicales Charles Ben Agreement (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Agreement between Octave and London Records, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - London Records (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Contracts between Phonogram (Sweden) and Octave (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Contract between Compagnia Generale Del Disco, Galleria Del Coso, Milan, Itlay and Octave Records (only part of contract) (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Ricordi Records (Italy) (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Nippon Columbia (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Television Licenses (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Harry Fox Agency (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1953-1975; 4.
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, Undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1950s (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1957-1960 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1960-1964 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Domestic Concert Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Contracts between Garner and William Morris Agency, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Performance Contracts: Garner's London Tour, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Cherry Lane: Contracts and Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - American Federation of Musicians, Correspondence and Agreements (Box 28, Folder 4-7)
    - Booking/Performance Agreements (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Contract Riders for Night Club Concerts (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Original Concert By The Sea Contract; Carmel, CA, September 19, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Copyright Documents, 1955-1977; 5.
    - Copyright (Correspondence, Contracts, Lists) (Box 28, Folder 11-16)
    - Certificates of Copyright Registration and Renewal Registration (Box 28, Folder 17-21)
    - Copyright Assignments (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - License Agreements (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Notices of Use (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Song Lists with Copyright Registration Numbers (Box 28, Folder 25-26)
    - Copyright Registration Forms for Tiny Grimes (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Tiny Grimes Licenses (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Misty Film Agreements & Related Documents, 1955-2001; 6.
    - Correspondence (and Contract) with Eastwood, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Misty Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Misty Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
    - Misty; Correspondence, Copyright, Agreements (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Misty; Correspondence, Licensing (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Misty Correspondence, re: Licensing (Box 29, Folder 7-9)
    - Misty Licenses (Box 29, Folder 10-11)
    - Misty Licenses to Columbia Pictures "Drive In" (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Misty Contract Transfer (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Misty Royalties - WB/Chappell (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Misty Warner/Chappell Publishing (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Play Misty For Me (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Play Misty For Me script (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Misty original copyright form (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Misty misc. ("Legal: Misty") (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Vernon Misty Legal Depositions, 1957; 7.
    - Legal Records, early contracts for Misty, etc./ Octave Music Publishing Corp. vs. Vernon Music Corp, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Octave Music Publishing Corp. Suit "o" Us-Vernon Music Corp. Deposition Exhibits (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Deposition Exhibits 1-15 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Deposition Exhibits 16-24 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Deposition Exhibits 25-30 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Deposition Exhibits 31-41 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Deposition Exhibits 42-47 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Deposition Exhibits 48-59 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Deposition Exhibits 60a-69 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Deposition Exhibits 70-72 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Deposition Exhibits 73-86 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Deposition Exhibits 87-95 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Deposition Exhibits 96-101 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Deposition Exhibits 102-106 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Deposition Exhibits 107-112 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Deposition Exhibits 113-123 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Deposition Erroll Garner Copy (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Deposition Robert Thiele Copy (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Deposition Robert Thiele Original (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Deposition Jack Bregman First Case (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Deposition Jack Bregman Copy (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Deposition Martha Glaser First Case (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Deposition A. Halsey Cowan Original (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Deposition A. Halsey Cowan Copy (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Erroll Garner Financial & Legal Documents, 1950-1975; 8.
    - Octave Music Publishing Corp. vs. Vernon Music Corp. & A. Halsey Cowan; A. Halsey Cowan Examination, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Defendant Vernon's Bill of Particulars Copy (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Defendant Vernon's Bill of Particulars Original (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Exhibit DB P 10 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Vernon Records, Octave, Misty (Box 31, Folder 5-7)
    - Octave vs. Vernon- Topical digest of deposition, testimony with exhibit references ( Misty) (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Misty/Vernon (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Garner vs. Gale Agency, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Harriet Joslyn vs. Garner, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Garner Business Letters, 1958-1986 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Garner Lawsuits (Box 31, Folder 13-14)
    - Garner Palomar Gardens Claim, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Copyright index cards (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Bootleg Disputes (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Garner- Financial (Box 31, Folder 18-19)
    - Erroll Garner Memorial Foundation Financial Records, 1977-1983 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Garner Business correspondence to Martha (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
    - Garner Non-Music Financial Inc. UK Income (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Garner Financial Records and Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Garner's Power of Attorney, will codicils (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Financial documents with Garner's signature (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
    - Erroll Garner Gross Earnings Reports, 1954-1960 (Box 32, Folder 8-13)
    - Kim Garner Paternity Records, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Visual & TV Licenses, 1955-1998; 9.
    - Garner-TV/Film/Radio Contracts, 1950-1959 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Paramount Pictures (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Paramount Pictures (A New Kind of Love), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - TV Contracts (pub) (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Television Licenses (requests, correspondence) (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Warner Brothers TV, Film & Records (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Garner-Ed Sullivan Show Agreements (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Kultur video- Garner in Performance (contract), June 18, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - TV contracts, 1967-1975 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - TV Agreements, 1960-1964 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Woody Allen Films (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Synchronization Licenses (Box 33, Folder 12-15)
    - Agreement Between Octave and 20th Century Fox (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Visual Licensing (Box 33, Folder 17-18)
    - Visual Licensing (Box 34, Folder 1-11)
    - Ed Sullivan "1001 Sundays" Project TV License (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Normandy Broadcasting Corporation (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Mr. Bean and Bumpy Music Inc. - Music Box Company (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Universal Music, Japan DVD (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Shawnee Mission East Band Boosters (high school band) - Lincoln Center (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Street performers of San Francisco (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Jeopardy TV use of Misty (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Martha Glaser Correspondence: "Like It Is" Dispute ABC TV / Down / Sillnoble / BBC (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - French TV film; "Jazz Memories" (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Dudley Moore/Palewell Productions film (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Music licenses, various compilations, etc. (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Record Labels Correspondence & Contracts, 1946-1975; 10.
    - Am-Par Records (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Arista Records (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Absolutely Kosher Records (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Fantasy/Prestige/Milestone (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Playboy Records (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - MGM Records (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Teresa Gramaphone (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - United Artists Records (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Onyx Records (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Telarc (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, Telarc International Corporation (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Twentieth Century Fox Records (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Koch (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Smithsonian Records (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Reader's Digest Records (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Shanacie Records (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Savoy Records (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Muzak (Box 35, Folder 1-4)
    - Garner Recording session bills, Capitol et al, October 30, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Contracts between Philips-Sonora and Octave, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Blue Note Records (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Contracts between Philips Phonographic Industries and Octave, 1963-1967 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Spotlight Records (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Misc. correspondence, Mercury Records & others (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 35, Folder 11-12)
    - Atlantic Music Agreement, July 2, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Capitol Songs Agreement, June 18, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Folkways Records (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Pye Records and Octave: contracts and correspondence (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Older Miscellaneous Non-Columbia Record Co. Statements (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Older Columbia Royalty Statements, 1950s (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Contract between Hurok and Garner, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Royalty correspondence (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Record Companies, 1945-1991; 11.
    - Misc. Record Companies; Correspondence & Agreements (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Deposition Martha Glaser (Box 36, Folder 2-3)
    - Lawsuit Octave vs. Vernon Music Corp. (Box 36, Folder 4-5)
    - Polygram/Polydor (Box 36, Folder 6-8)
    - RCA Records (Box 36, Folder 9-13)
    - Warner Brothers (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Miramax (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Mercury Contracts (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Criterion Contracts (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Crown Records--Fraud Matter (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Vogue Records (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Jazz Groove Records (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Hindsight Records Inc. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Mercury, Am-Par, Polygram, Philips, American Federation of Musicians (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - MPS Records, unsigned (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Octave Music Documents, 1952-2005; 12.
    Subseries includes original management agreement between Erroll Garner and Martha Glaser.
    - Criterion Agreement (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence RE: Old Contracts, 1950s (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Shake It, But Don't Break It (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Chemical Bank and Octave (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Misc. Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Contract and Correspondence between Ashley-Famous Agency and Garner, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Contract and Correspondence between Associated Booking Corp. and Garner, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Contract and Correspondence between Sutton Artists Corp. and Garner, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Contract and Correspondence between Octave and Barclay International, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Contract and Correspondence between Octave and Reader's Digest, 1976-1982 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence; Re: Book of the Month Club contract, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Contracts between Valando Music Corp and Octave Music, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Recording Sessions/Financials; RE: Associated Musicians of NY (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - American Society of Composers, Authors & Publishers (ASCAP) agreement and membership (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Agreement between American Society of Composers, Authors & Publishers (ASCAP) and Garner, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Records Sessions: contracts and bills (between Octave and various studios) (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Compulsory Licenses (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Agreements between Garner/Octave (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Misc. Contracts (Octave) (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Octave Music Publishing Corporation (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Octave Music Financial Records (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Erroll Garner Misc. Non-Music Financial Records (Box 37, Folder 30-31)
    - Erroll Garner Octave (Box 37, Folder 32-34)
    - Agreements between Garner/Octave; Incorporation Papers- Octave (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Erroll Garner: contract, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Octave Minutes, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Octave Minutes-Blank Forms (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Octave Stock Certificates (Box 38, Folder 5-7)
    - Octave Stock and Transfer Lodger (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Sony/Columbia Dispute Legal Documents, 1950-2001; 13.
    - Sony/Columbia/CBS Royalties (Box 38, Folder 9-10)
    - CBS Records-- Concert By The Sea (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Columbia Licenses (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Plaintiff Exhibits for EBT of NA 97, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - New York Supreme Court, Erroll Enterprises, Inc. and Erroll Garner against Columbia Records, A Division of Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc.- Papers on Appeal Form Orders, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Plaintiff's Exhibits from EBT of MM, 1956-1959 (Box 38, Folder 15-16)
    - CBS/Sony (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Concert By The Sea (Sony) (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Columbia Letters etc. (Rec) (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Erroll Garner: Columbia Records (correspondence) (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Agreement of Settlement and Correspondence--Garner and Columbia, 1962-1964 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Contract and Correspondence between CBS and Erroll Enterprises, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Agreements between CBS and Octave, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Franklin Mint Project--Columbia Records (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Columbia Lawsuit Correspondence and News Coverage (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
    - Columbia Agreement, June 1, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Columbia Settlement Agreement, July 25, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Sony Music Entertainment Licensing Agreements, 1995-2003 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Columbia Lawsuit documents and correspondence, 1950s-1960s (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Martha Glaser correspondence with Columbia Broadcasting Systems (CBS), 1960s-1980s (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Royalty Examination of Sony Music, Inc. On Behalf of the Estate of Erroll Garner (2) (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
    - Copies of 1956-1961 Docs (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Garner vs. Columbia--Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Exhibits & Correspondence- Erroll Enterprises, Inc. & Erroll Garner vs. Columbia Records A Div. Columbia Broadcasting System (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Suit--Erroll Enterprises Inc., et al vs. Columbia Records (Box 39, Folder 13-15)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- Publicity and Press Releases (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- Agreement between Octave Records Inc. and Am-Par Record Corp. and Supplementary Letter, March 27, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- Octave-Am-Par Second Contract & Supplementary Letter, June 1, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- Counsels' Letter re: Minimum Number of Albums to be Sold (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- Proposed Contract with United Stereo Tapes (Not used) (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- Authorization to Harry Fox by Octave Music (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- Audit of Columbia Records, re: Erroll Garner (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- License from Octave Music to Synthetic Plastics (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- European Trip, May 26-June 10, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- Moe Asch (Folkways Records & Service Corp.)--Releases (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- Power of Attorney from Erroll Garner to Martha Glaser (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- Outlines of Proposed Agreements between Octave and Mercury AND Octave-Mercury re: Tiny Grimes (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Legal Portfolio; Folder #226- Copy of Agreement between Octave Records, Inc. and United Artists Records, Inc. (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Columbia Lawsuit Depositions, 1950-1990; 14.
    - Correspondence: Garner vs. Columbia (Box 39, Folder 29-32)
    - Legal Court Documents (Box 40, Folder 1-10)
  - Erroll Garner Memorial Foundation Documents, 1990s; 15.
    - Erroll Garner charities, scholarships, memorial foundation (Box 40, Folder 11-14)
    - Erroll Garner foundation scholarship applicants (Box 40, Folder 15-16)
    - Hector G. Dowd, Attorney (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Martha Glaser beneficiary correspondence-Screen Actors Guild (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Settlement of Gale/American Federation of Music dispute (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Sankyo dispute, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence re: Postage stamp (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Photographs, V.
  The Photographs series contains prints, negatives and transparencies featuring Erroll Garner's performances, recording studio activities, travels as well as with other notable recording artists and celebrities of the day. Many of the photographs were used for promotional purposes such as album covers and advertising. Photographs in this series are from varied sources including record companies, wire service photographers, and freelance photographers such as African-American photographer Charles Stewart and director Aram Avakian. Original folder titles are represented.
  - 3D Photo Objects & Miscellaneous, 1.
    - Paperwork related to photographs (Box 41, Folder 1)
      Correspondence relating to use, release, and purchase of Erroll Garner images.
    - Letter referring to possible Richard Avedon photo (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - B&W Montage prints, 11 photographs (Box 41, Folder 3)
      Montages of Erroll performing and Erroll headshots.
    - Color Touring, 6 items (Box 41, Folder 4)
      Prints of Erroll at piano and letter from Martha Glaser re: return of prints.
    - Color Candid, 29 photographs (Box 41, Folder 5)
      Portraits of Erroll Garner, a house in California, copy photograph of Erroll Garner painted portrait.
    - Color Candid, 25 photographs (Box 41, Folder 6)
      Portraits of Erroll Garner, Erroll Garner with Sylvia Syms, Christmas photos, photos at a California house.
    - Color Publicity, 25 photographs (Box 41, Folder 7)
      Photos from a Merle Shore photo shoot, Erroll performing, cut-out headshot.
    - Miscellaneous photos, 83 items (Box 41, Folder 8)
      Business cards; correspondence; photos from Erroll Garner's Carnegie Hall show; assorted portraits of Erroll Garner, Martha Glaser, and others; news clippings; assorted other photographs.
    - Miscellaneous photos, 49 items (Box 41, Folder 9)
      Photos of Erroll Garner in the recording studio, news clippings, photos of others, road trip photos, Erroll Garner poster, photos of house and music store.
    - Miscellaneous photos, 3 photographs (Box 41, Folder 10)
      Portraits of Erroll Garner at the piano.
    - Miscellaneous photos, 4 photographs (Box 41, Folder 11)
      Portraits of Erroll Garner leaning against a wall.
    - Miscellaneous photos, 3 photographs (Box 41, Folder 12)
      Portrait of Erroll Garner looking over a ledge.
    - Miscellaneous photos, 6 photographs (Box 41, Folder 13)
      Portraits of Erroll Garner.
    - Les Gould, Philips England (touring, studio, publicity), 19 items (Box 41, Folder 14)
      Portrait of Erroll Garner with a Swedish friend; portraits taken in a recording studio.
    - Cherry Lane Songbook, 10 photographs (Box 41, Folder 15)
      Assorted portraits of Erroll Garner.
    - Bill Farrell – singer, 18 photographs (Box 41, Folder 16)
      Assorted photos of singer Bill Farrell.
    - Tiny Grimes, 2 photographs (Box 41, Folder 17)
      Photos of Tiny Grimes performing.
    - Art prints by Hirschfield, 12 items (Box 41, Folder 18)
      Originals & Photocopies of drawings of Erroll Garner.
    - Photos from fans, 21 photographs (Box 41, Folder 19)
      Assorted fan photos sent to Erroll Garner and do not include Garner.
    - Photocopies (Box 41, Folder 20-23)
    - Miscellaneous Photocopies (Box 41, Folder 24-26)
    - Oversized photocopies (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Charles "Teenie" Harris Photocopies (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Martha Glaser ID photos in Garner archive (photocopies) (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Photo Engraving Plates, 2 items (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Images of Garner's face, 24 slides (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Silver-plated printing plates (2), with Erroll portrait, 4 items (Box 41, Folder 32)
      Printing plates and cardboard printing stamps.
    - Wood block metal printing plates, 3 items (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Black and White Candids, Studio, 2.
    - B&W Candid, 20 photographs (Box 42, Folder 1)
      Assorted photos of Erroll Garner with others.
    - B&W Candid, 15 photographs (Box 42, Folder 2)
      Assorted photos of Erroll Garner.
    - Basin Street, November 1955; 1 photograph (Box 42, Folder 3)
      Portrait of Erroll Garner with British jazz pianist, Leonard Feather (1914-1994) and German-born jazz pianist, Jutta Hipp (1925-2003).
    - Basin Street, November 1954; 8 photographs (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Birthday 35th, June 15, 1956; 1 photograph (Box 42, Folder 5)
      Erroll Garner with three men at a birthday celebration.
    - Garner and Robert Vaughn, 2 photographs (Box 42, Folder 6)
      Erroll Garner with actor Robert Vaughn (1932-)
    - B&W Candid Promo (multiple copies), 5 photographs (Box 42, Folder 7)
      Portraits of Erroll at the piano and in the recording studio.
    - B&W Candid Promo (multiple copies), 2 photographs (Box 42, Folder 8)
      Erroll Garner and others in a recording studio.
    - B&W Candid Promo (multiple copies), 33 photographs (Box 42, Folder 9)
      Photos of Erroll Garner receiving an award from the Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh as well as assorted photos taken in the recording studio.
    - Garner Birthday EMI England, 1966; 3 items (Box 42, Folder 10)
      Erroll Garner celebrating his birthday at the EMI Studios and related correspondence.